typicallyspanish.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Page - Spain news - Topsite for Spanish News in English - TypicallySpanish.com -

### Typically Spanish - PRIVACY POLICY

www.typicallyspanish.com website does not collect any personal information without your knowledge or transfer it to third parties.

We can, however, disclose personal data to comply with legal requirements, demand the enforcement of our policies, respond to claims relating to infringement by advertisements or other content of third party rights, or to protect the rights of any person or property or their safety.

### Contact email

The contact email [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com) is designed as where citizens can access our services and aims, in accordance with Article 37.e) of Law 15/1999 of 13 December on the Protection of Personal Data, to provide information to people about their rights regarding treatment of personal data.

The personal data you provide by e-mail is recorded in the **database owned by Howard Brereton, NIE X0892424R and address C /Los Huertos, 83, Edificio Coronado, Entrance 1, Apartment 62, 29780 Nerja (Málaga),** who aims to answer any of your questions and who also may obtain statistical data from them.  
This page is purely informative, and does not in any case, provide answers of binding legal effect.

### Right of access, opposition, rectification and cancellation

 **The registered user can manage their communications and exercise rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition, attaching a copy of the NIF, NIE, CIF, by writing, in the same terms, Howard J. Brereton with address at C / Los Huertos, 83, Edificio Coronado, Entrance 1, Apartment 62, 29780 Nerja (Málaga)**

### Links

This privacy policy applies only to the website www.typicallyspanish.com, and does not cover access via links to this site, or links from this site to other websites.

### Automatically logged information

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

### Cookies

Our site uses cookies in the Directory for convenice. It remembers you when you log in. Plus, our third party advert serving system with Double Click and Google ads does use cookies. (see below)

### Advertisers

We use a third party advertising company to display ads on our site. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertising company and we have no access to this information.

### Google

We use third-party advertising companies to place ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites, in order to provide advertisements targeted to your preferences in goods and services. For more information about this practice and inform you of your options if you do not want these companies to use this information, [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/).

### Direct Advertisers

In order to issue an official invoice, we ask everyone who purchases banner ads or any other advertising or sponsorship on our site, to provide the full corporate name, address and CIF. We charge 21% VAT on all invoices to companies located in Spain. The VAT is not charged to firms located outside Spain. The information collected in this manner is maintained by us and never made available to third parties. 

### Payments and Credit Cards

### Collection of Statistical Data

This site does not collect or store personal data of its visitors.

Only, in order to provide the best service through this page, and in order to facilitate its use, we analyze the number of pages viewed, the number of visits, and the activity of visitors to the web, and their frequency of use.

For this purpose, we use the statistical data compiled by the Internet Service Provider of www.typicallyspanish.com and also Google.inc

The Privacy Policy of Google is in the <http://www.google.es/privacypolicy.html>

With this information we can analyse the visitor numbers of www.typicallyspanish.com from the connection data and determine the most visited sections and pages. 

### Email Communications and Tools

You consent to receive commercial communications from us in your email or any other similar means, unless you notify us that prefer not to receive such communications. If you do not want to receive commercial communications, simply follow the instructions provided in each communication.

You may not use www.typicallyspanish.com as a communication tool to collect addresses, send spam or violate any of our Terms and Conditions or our Privacy Policy. We may revise or filter your messages automatically or manually to monitor malicious activity or prohibited content but we do not store messages permanently. If the user uses our tools to send content to friends, we do not permanently store the addresses or use or disclose this data for sending commercial communications. Please contact [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com) to report the spam made by other users. 

### Feedback from users of Typically Spanish

www.typicallyspanish.com is not responsible for the opinions of third parties that have been published in the media, and can be disseminated through the section 'comments' on news pages, as well as the opinions published in the section of directory 'reviews'. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and must exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Email Communications and Tools

You consent to receive commercial communications from us in your email or any other similar means, unless you notify us that prefer not to receive such communications. If you do not want to receive commercial communications, simply follow the instructions provided in each communication.

You may not use www.typicallyspanish.com as a communication tool to collect addresses, send spam or violate any of our Terms and Conditions or our Privacy Policy. We may revise or filter your messages automatically or manually to monitor malicious activity or prohibited content but we do not store messages permanently. If the user uses our tools to send content to friends, we do not permanently store the addresses or use or disclose this data for sending commercial communications. Please contact urgent@typicallyspanish.com to report the spam made by other users. 

### Opting Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving promotional information from us or marketing.  
1\. By email to [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com)  
2\. By telephone (+34) 722263512  

### Security

We use many tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect our users' personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, without prejudice to the Internet security measures which may not be infallible, and therefore we cannot guarantee anything in this area.

### General and Updates

We may update this policy at any time. The updates take effect IN one of the following two circumstances: when the user uses the website, or once 30 days have elapsed since the update.   
If we are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal data about our users with another company, but this policy will continue to apply.   
Please send questions about this policy to [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com).

### Data Quality and Access

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You can use the same contact if not satisfied with any comments about your company in our comments section.  
1\. By email to [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com)  
2\. By telephone (+34) 722263512

### Contacting the Website

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. You can use the same contact if not satisfied with any comments about your company in our comments section.  
1\. By email to [feedback@typicallyspanish.com](mailto:feedback@typicallyspanish.com)  
2\. By telephone (+34) 722263512 3\. By contact form [click here](http://www.typicallyspanish.com/form/contactform.shtml)
